Guide to the Thomas Raynesford Lounsbury Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, Series I
  - Elson, William H., 1905 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Elton, Oliver, 1894 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Ely, Abbie, 1884 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Ely, S. W., 1907 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Embree, Edwin Rogers, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Emerson, Godfrey, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Emerson, Oliver Farrar, 1892-1893 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Emery, Fred Parker, 1891 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Emery, Henry C., 1903 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Entler, George R., 1882 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Ernst, C. W., 1911 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Erskine, John, 1902-1903 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Esbjorn, C. L., 1914 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Eshbaugh, Daniel O., 1898 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Estes, Wyatt Collier, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Evans, E. F., 1893 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Evans, F. Waldron, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Evans, W. L., 1889 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Evans, William Darlington, 1906-1915 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Evening Post
    See: Rollo Ogden, box 16, folder 341
  - Everett, William, 1893-1902 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - F - General (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Fairbanks, Edward, 1886-1909 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Farnam, Charles Henry, 1880 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Farnam, Henry Walcott(*), 1882-1904 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Farnam, Susan Strong, 1894-1896 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Farnam, William Whitman, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Farnum, Emily J., 1913 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Farr, Hollon Augustine, 1899 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Farrand, Beatrix (Mrs. Max), undated (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Farwell, Granger, undated (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Farwell, Margaret, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Faulkner, Charles James, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Faulkner, Herbert W., 1906 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Faulkner, Samuel D., 1872 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Faxon, F. W., 1895-1896 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Fay, H. W., 1886 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Feeter, George E., 1894 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Fenn, Willis J., 1888 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Fenton, J., 1881 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Fernald, Fred, 1891-1895 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Ferris, G. T., 1886 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Ferry, Charles Herbert, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Field, Mrs. Jennie J.(*), 1882-1897 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Fields, William T., 1884-1898 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Finlay, Prof., 1906 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Finley, John Huston, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Firth, C. H., 1902 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Fish, Benjamin, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Fish, Job, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Fisher, Anna A., 1911, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Fisher, Dorothy (Canfield)
    See: Dorothy Canfield, box 3, folder 71
  - Fisher, George Park, 1885-1905 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Fisher, Herbert Wilson, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Fisher, Irving, 1888-1913 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Fiske, Christabel Forsyth, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Fiske, D. Willard(*), 1872-1898 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Fisler, S. L., 1895 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Fitch, Gilbert, 1899 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Fitch, Henry H., 1874 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Fitzmaurice, Lady Caroline, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Fitzsimons, John Essex, 1885 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Fleisher, David, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Fletcher, Horace, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Flexner, Simon, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Flood, Theodore, 1889 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Flü, Ewald, 1889-1895 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Folwell, Adelaide(*), 1872-1894 (Box 6, Folder 151-153)
  - Folwell, Florence Doty (Mrs. Mahlon Bainbridge), 1882-1904 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Folwell, Jennie Dungan
    See: Jennie Dungan (Folwell) Lounsbury, box 12, folders 280-283
  - Folwell, Joanna B., 1889 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Folwell, Mahlon Bainbridge(*), 1871-1895 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Folwell, Mary H., 1909-1912 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Folwell, Sarah H., 1903-1915 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Folwell, William Watts(*), 1871-1913 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Forbes, Edwin Horace, 1894-1898 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Ford, George W., 1872-1875 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Ford, Vincent, 1886 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Forman, William Henry, 1883 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Forrest, James, 1885 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Fortescue-Cole, John, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Foss, Martin M., 1906 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Foster, Catherine L., 1912 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Foster, E. K., 1874 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Foster, H. M., 1908 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Foster, H. W., 1876 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Foushee, William L., 1909 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Fox, Charles J., undated (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Fox, George Levi, 1892-1897 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Fox, S. M., 1914 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Fox, Thomas A., 1895 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Frances, W. R., 1887 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Francis, David R., 1905 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Freeland, Arthur Graham, 1893-1895 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Fridenberg, Dr. Percy, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Frissell, Hollis Burke, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Frommel, Ernest H., 1906 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Frothingham, Arthur Lincoln, 1885 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Fuller, A. C., 1895 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Fuller, Howard de Wolf, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Funk, Issac K.(*), 1894-1911 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Furness, Horace Howard(*), 1901-1911 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Furness, Horace Howard, Jr., 1903-1913 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Furnivall, Frederick J.(*), 1877-1908 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - G - General (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Gaffey, John F., 1885 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Gage, W. L., 1874 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Gage, William T., 1874 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Gaillard, William D., 1908 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Gallaher, Frank Runyon, 1894 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Galpin, Samuel Arthur, 1886-1902 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Gardner, Bertha L., 1913 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Gardner, Ellen D., 1904 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Garland, Hamlin, 1900-1904 (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Garnett, James M., 1875-1900 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Garrison, Elisha, 1896 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Garrison, Henry, 1875 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Garrison, Wendell P.(*), 1874-1892 (Box 7, Folder 171-172)
  - Gass, W., 1898 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Gaston, Charles Robert, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Gatlin, Dana, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Gayley, Charles Mills, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Geiger, Harvey, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Georger, Louis F., 1886-1887 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Gibbs, J. Willard, 1887-1900 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Gibbs, Wolcott, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Gilbert, Annie, 1894 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Gilchrist, Alexander(*), 1871-1912 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Gilder, Joseph B.(*), 1884-1913 (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1890-1908 (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Gildersleeve, Basil, 1879 (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Gillespie, John, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Gilman, Arthur, 1879-1903 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1873-1894 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Gilmore, James P., 1888-1890 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Gilmore, Laura E., 1889 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Gilmour, Andrew J., 1894 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Ginn, Edwin(*), 1877-1908 (Box 7, Folder 180-181)
  - Ginn & Co.(*), 1873-1905 (Box 7, Folder 182-184)
  - Girdwood, H. D., 1902 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Gladwin, Irving C., 1886 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Glenny, William Henry, Jr., 1893 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Goe, Theodore J., 1907 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Golden, Harry C., 1909 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Goodell, Thomas D., 1895 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey, 1908 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Goodrich, E. P., 1886 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Goodrich, Hattie, 1888 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Goodwin, F. A., 1885 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Goodwin, William Watson, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Gordon, Armistead, 1908 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Gordon, William W., 1885 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Gosse, Edmund, 1885-1911 (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - Gould, J. Avery, 1906 (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - Graham, Wilson, 1891 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Grandgent, Charles, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Grannis, Ruth, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Grant, William L., 1914 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Grantham, Muriel, undated (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Graves, Albert, 1873-1892 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Grazebrook, Maud, 1908 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Greanelle, W. D., 1908 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Green, Charles Ewing, undated (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Green, Francis Harvey, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Green, George Walton, 1885 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Greene, Belle da Costa, 1904-1915 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Greene, Herbert Eveleth, 1895 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Greene, Mary A., 1896 (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Greene, Nelson, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Greenough, Mrs. Horation, 1882 (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Griffin, Charles, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Griffin, J. G, 1913-1914 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Griffin, Mattie, 1908 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Griswold, William, 1885 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Grove, Abram, 1891 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Gruener, Gustav, 1892-1906 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Gruener, Henry Robert, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Grumbine, H. C., 1913 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Gudebrod, Louis A., 1905 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Gulick, Edward L., 1895 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Gummere, Francis, undated (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Gunckel, Lewis B., 1890 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - H - General (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Hackett, E. Byrne(*), 1910-1915 (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - Hackett, Frank W., 1911-1912 (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - Hadley, Arthur Twining, 1891-1912 (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Hadley, James, 1859-1867 (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Hagen, Winston, 1907 (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Haines, H. S.(*), 1897-1904 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Hale, M. C., 1889 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Hale, William Bayard, 1907 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Hale, William G., 1893-1894 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Hall, Charles E., .1884-1885 (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Hall, Fitz-Edward, 1898-1900 (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Hall, John E. M., 1875 (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Hall, John Lesslie, 1885-1913 (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - Hamersly, T. H. S., 1881-1882 (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - Hamill, Susan Walbridge, 1880 (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - Hamlin, Harry L., 1886-1888 (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Hammel, W. C. A., 1908 (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Hammond, John Hays, 1900-1906 (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Hanlin, Clara, 1906 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Hannah, Niles Carrington, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Hannahs, John Jay, 1890 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Hannigan, Mrs. John Edward, 1907 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Hannum, William M., 1904 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Hanscom, Elizabeth D., 1895 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Harland, Aline, 1892 (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - Harman, Ralph A., 1906 (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - Harman, Sue Wade, 1906 (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - Harper, George McLean, 1905-1912 (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - Harper, Joseph W., 1908 (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - Harper, Joseph Wesley, Jr., 1890 (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - Harper, William, 1882-1897 (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - Harper, William. R., 1892 (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - Harper, and Brothers(*), 1890-1914 (Box 8, Folder 203-204)
    See also: F. A. Duneka, box 5, folder 123
  - Harper's
    See: Henry Mills Alden, box 1, folder 6 See: Samuel S. Conant, box 4, folder 91 See: Henry E. Rood, box 18, folder 387
  - Harris, G. William, 1882 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Harris, J. F., 1892 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Harris, Laura Houghton, 1911-1914 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Harris, M. A., 1900 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Harris, N. Dwight, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Harrison, Burton N., 1878 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Harrison, Calvin L., 1887 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Harrison, Caskie, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Harrison, Francis Burton, 1895 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Harrison, James A., 1882-1883 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Harrison, William G., 1883 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Hart, Charles Henry, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Hart, James Morgan(*), 1876-1899 (Box 9, Folder 207)
  - Hart, John G., 1904 (Box 9, Folder 207)
  - Hart, John M., 1874 (Box 9, Folder 207)
  - Hartford Courant
    See: Charles Hopkins Clark, box 4, folder 84
  - Hartman, Lee Foster, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Hartranft, Chester D., 1893 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Hartwell, Edward M., 1913 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Hasbrouck, J. L., 1882 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Haskell, Louise W., undated (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Haskell, Willabe, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Hastings, E. J., 1905-1906 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Hastings, Thomas, 1899 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Hatch, Charles H., 1875 (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Hatch, Frank L., 1892-1893 (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Hathaway, Charles M., 1903 (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Havemeyer, John F., 1895 (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Haven, George A., 1912 (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Haweis Hugh Reginald, 1885 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Haweis, Mary E., 1887 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Hawes, Edward S., 1899 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Hawes, George W., 1882 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Hawkin, T. Duffield, 1906-1908 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Hawley, Frederick, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Hawley, Joseph, 1884 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Hayes, George W., 1908 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Hayes, William A., 1896 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Haynes, Thornwell, 1895 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Hays, Anne K., 1911 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Hazard, Mary P., 1905 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Hazard, Rowland, 1881, 1904-1906 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Hazel, G. W., 1898-1899 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Hazen, M. B., 1910 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Head, Frazier D., 1886 (Box 9, Folder 212)
  - Heath, Daniel Collamore, 1885 (Box 9, Folder 212)
    See: Charles Henry Douglas, box 5, folder 119
  - Heaton, John, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 212)
  - Heim, Marion, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 212)
  - Hemingway, Samuel B., 1905-1914 (Box 9, Folder 212)
  - Hempl, George, 1895-1911 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Hempstead, C., 1890 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Hendrick, Burton, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Hendrickson, George, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Hendrickson, Marion Vaux, 1912 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Henneman, John, 1896-1901 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Henry, Aurelia, 1904-1905 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Herrmann, Charles W., 1878 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Herts, B. Russell, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Hewett, Waterman T., 1905 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Hibbard, Harry, 1878 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Hickok, William Orville, 1895 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Hider, Arthur Spotswood, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth, 1883-1904 (Box 9, Folder 215)
  - Hiles, Ogden, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 215)
  - Hill, Ebenezer, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 215)
  - Hill, Edith Healy, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 215)
  - Hill, G. Birkbeck(*), 1892-1902 (Box 9, Folder 216)
  - Hill, William Barlow, 1889-1892 (Box 9, Folder 216)
  - Himes, John Andrew, 1873-1913 (Box 9, Folder 216)
  - Hinckley, Henry Barrett(*), 1894-1913 (Box 9, Folder 217)
  - Hinckley, Henry R., 1896 (Box 9, Folder 217)
  - Hitchcock, Alfred M., 1905 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Hitchcock, Frank Harris, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Hitchcock, James Ripley, 1898-1912 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Hoadley, Charles, 1874-1880 (Box 9, Folder 218)
  - Hobles, Edwin, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 219)
  - Hobson, A. E., 1893 (Box 9, Folder 219)
  - Hockenberry, W. H., 1905 (Box 9, Folder 219)
  - Hodell, Charles W., 1906 (Box 9, Folder 219)
  - Hodge, Edwin, 1886 (Box 9, Folder 219)
  - Hodgkins, Louise M.(*), 1882-1913 (Box 9, Folder 220)
  - Hoe, Robert, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Holbrook, Richard, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Holcombe, John, 1886 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Holden, Edward, 1879-1880 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Holland, J. G., 1878 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Hollister, O. J., 1886 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Holt, Charles, 1880 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Holt, Florence Taber (Mrs. Henry), 1913 (Box 9, Folder 221)
  - Holt, Henry(*), 1872-1909 (Box 9, Folder 222-223)
  - Holt, Henry and Co.(*), 1877-1910 (Box 10, Folder 224-225)
  - Holt, Lucius Hudson, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 226)
  - Holt, Roland(*), 1891-1914 (Box 10, Folder 226)
  - Holzheimer, Charles W., undated (Box 10, Folder 226)
  - Honey, Edith Shavely, undated (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Honey, Frederick R., 1878 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Hoover, Theodore, 1915 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Hopkins, Edward Washburn, 1903-1905 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Hopkins, Edwin M., 1897 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Hopkins, Louis R., 1895 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Hoppin, James Mason, 1900-1903 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Hoppin, Susan Mitchell, undated (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Horsey, Elisa Lee, 1884 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Horton, Maud M., 1911 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Hosmer, Edith T., 1906 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Hosmer, James K., 1880 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Hotchkiss, Howard P., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Hotz, Christopher, 1888-1889 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Hough, Benjamin Kent, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Houghteling, James Lawrence, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Houghton, Mabelle, 1911 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Houghton, Mifflin & Co.(*), 1881-1914 (Box 10, Folder 229)
  - Hovey, George Rice, 1910 (Box 10, Folder 230)
  - Howard, E. L. B., 1909 (Box 10, Folder 230)
  - Howe, Will D., 1904-1905 (Box 10, Folder 230)
  - Howell, Dewitt(*), 1885-1894 (Box 10, Folder 231)
  - Howells, William Dean(*), 1876-1909 (Box 10, Folder 232)
  - Howland, Clarence, 1894 (Box 10, Folder 233)
  - Howland, Frances L.(*), 1909-1914 (Box 10, Folder 233)
  - Howland, Judge Henry K.(*), 1893-1911 (Box 10, Folder 234)
  - Hoyt, Franklin J., 1895-1897 (Box 10, Folder 234)
  - Hoyt, Henry M., 1910 (Box 10, Folder 234)
  - Huard, Frances Wilson, 1912 (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Hubbard, Elbert, 1905-1911 (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Hubbard, Robert Dudley, 1879 (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1905 (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Hulbert, Homer B., 1908 (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Humphrys, Ernest, 1904-1905 (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Hunt, Mrs. Augusta M., 1906 (Box 10, Folder 236)
  - Hunt, Henry D., 1893-1895 (Box 10, Folder 236)
  - Hunt, Theodore Whitefield, 1885-1890 (Box 10, Folder 236)
  - Hunter, Mrs. F. D., 1913 (Box 10, Folder 236)
  - Huntington, Alice, 1892 (Box 10, Folder 236)
  - Huntington, Archer Milton(*), 1892-1913 (Box 10, Folder 237)
  - Huntington, Gertrude Lea, undated (Box 10, Folder 237)
  - Huntoon, Edmee B., 1911 (Box 10, Folder 237)
  - Huntting, E. M., 1906 (Box 10, Folder 237)
  - Hurd, O. P., 1891 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Huse, Hiram A., 1873 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Huston, Paul Griswold, 1903 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Hutchings, Samuel, 1883 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Hutchings, William Evelyn, 1885 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Hutchins, D. E., 1913 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Hutchins, George P., 1902 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Hutchinson, Ellen Mackay
    See: Ellen Mackay (Hutchinson) Cortissoz, box 4, folder 99
  - Hutton, Addison, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Hutton, Hilda E., 1909 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Hutton, Laurence(*), 1883-1904 (Box 10, Folder 239)
  - Hyde, Dora B. Keith (Mrs. Frank E.), 1900-1909 (Box 10, Folder 239)
  - I - General (Box 10, Folder 240)
  - Ingersoll, Charles A., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - Ingersoll, Colin McCrae, 1888-1893 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - Inglesby, Clement, 1878 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - Ingram, Henry Atlee, 1877 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - International Review
    See: A. S. Barnes, box 1, folder 24 See: Henry Cabot Lodge, box 12, folder 276
  - Isaacs, Winnie, 1910 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - Isham, Samuel, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - Ives, Robert Shoemaker, 1878 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - J - General (Box 10, Folder 242)
  - Jackson, A. V. Williams, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 243)
  - Jackson, Charles Loring, 1894-1895 (Box 10, Folder 243)
  - Jackson, Huntington W., 1895 (Box 10, Folder 243)
  - Jackson, John Day, 1904 (Box 10, Folder 243)
  - Jackson, Joseph Cooke, 1887 (Box 10, Folder 243)
  - Jaffray, Robert, 1872 (Box 10, Folder 244)
  - Jaffray, Robert, Jr., 1909 (Box 10, Folder 244)
  - James, W. E., 1909 (Box 10, Folder 244)
  - James, William, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 244)
  - Jameson, John Franklin, 1896-1913 (Box 10, Folder 244)
  - Jamison, Blaine, 1880 (Box 10, Folder 244)
  - Janeway, Theodore, 1904 (Box 10, Folder 244)
  - Jastrow, Joseph, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 244)
  - Jefferson, Joseph, 1896 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Jeffries, Henry A., 1905 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Jelke, F. Frazier, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Jelliffe, Roberta, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Jenkins, Edward Hopkins, 1892-1909 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Jenkins, Elizabeth Eliot Foote (Mrs. Edward), 1907-1915 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Jessup, Alexander, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Jewel, Ross, 1905 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Jewett, Charles S., 1884-1906 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Jobs, Thomas A., 1893 (Box 11, Folder 246)
  - Johns, Tude T., 1907 (Box 11, Folder 246)
  - Johnson, Alexander, 1891 (Box 11, Folder 246)
  - Johnson, Charles F., 1900-1913 (Box 11, Folder 246)
  - Johnson, Charles W.L., 1905 (Box 11, Folder 246)
  - Johnson, Edward H., 1883 (Box 11, Folder 246)
  - Johnson, Edwin E., 1879 (Box 11, Folder 246)
  - Johnson, F. W., 1913 (Box 11, Folder 247)
  - Johnson, H. F., 1913 (Box 11, Folder 247)
  - Johnson, Henry, 1887 (Box 11, Folder 247)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood(*), 1884-1915 (Box 11, Folder 248)
  - Johnson, S. W., undated (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - Johnson, W. Woolsey, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - Johnston, Alexander, 1883 (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - Johnston, D. V. R., 1897 (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - Johnston, Henry P., 1908 (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - Johnston, James C. M., undated (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - Johnston, William Preston, 1893 (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - Johnstone, Robert, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - Jones, Amanda, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Jones, Dr. Daniel Albion, 1895 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Jones, Edward, 1882 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Jones, Frank J., 1898 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Jones, H. S. V., 1913 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Jones, Henry Arthur, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Jones, Herbert, 1892-1893 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Jones, Lawrence, 1897 (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Jordan, David Starr, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - Jordan, Mary A.(*), 1885-1895 (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - Jost, Frederic William, 1890 (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - Journal of English and Germanic Philology, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - Joy, Charles A.(*), 1875-1891 (Box 11, Folder 252)
  - Joy, Elizabeth Fletcher(Mrs. Clarence Schuyler Joy), 1908 (Box 11, Folder 252)
  - Joy, Henrietta, 1906 (Box 11, Folder 252)
  - Joy, Laura R. (Mrs. Charles A.)(*), 1875-1902 (Box 11, Folder 253-254)
  - Joynes, Edward S., 1880 (Box 11, Folder 255)
  - Judah, Mary Jameson (Mrs. John. M.), 1894 (Box 11, Folder 255)
  - Jusserand, Jean Adrien Antoine Jules, 1896-1907 (Box 11, Folder 255)
  - K - General (Box 11, Folder 256)
  - Kaines, Richard, 1890 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Kaiser, Ferd. P., 1900 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Kane, James M., 1914 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Karr, Louise, 1906 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Keeler, Lucy Elliot, 1892 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Keeler, William H., 1891 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Keen, William W., 1908-1913 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Kelby, William, 1882 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - Kelley, Edgar Stillman, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Kelley, Jessie (Mrs. Edgar S.), 1902-1914 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Kellogg, B., 1879 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Kendall, Calvin Meyer, 1906 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Kendall, Edward G., 1899 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Kendrick, Sarah, 1893 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Kennedy, Daniel Edwards, 1905 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Keogh, Andrew, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Kerlin, Robert T., 1913 (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - Kershner, Jefferson, 1899 (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - Kilbourne, Frederick W., 1894-1899 (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - Kimball, Charles W., 1873 (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - King, C. W., 1902 (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - King, Grace, 1887-1913 (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - Kingsbury, Fred J., 1885 (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - Kingsley, Mrs. Henry C., undated (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - Kingsley, William L., 1873 - [1895?] (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - Kinkead, George B., 1899 (Box 11, Folder 260)